Firebase is a action, science fiction, war film directed by Neill Blomkamp.
Set during the Vietnam war, Firebase follows American soldier Hines
through an ever-deepening web of science fiction madness.
Sgt. Hines, played by Steve Boyle.
Jacob Palmer, played by Nic Rhind.
Sgt. Carr, played by Robert Hobbs.
Maj. Brickerson, played by Chris William Martin.
Sgt. Bracken, played by Tyler Johnston.
River God, played by Carlo Yu.
Firebase was a company that developed backend software.
It was founded in San Francisco in 2011 and was incorporated in Delaware.
In 2014, Firebase was bought by Google.
Its name continues as a set of backend cloud computing services and
application development platforms provided by Google.
It hosts databases, services, authentication, and integration for a variety of
applications, including Android, iOS, JavaScript, Node.js, Java, Unity, PHP, and C++.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.